Kar Do
[Music]
Se Come Welcome to my channel Care For You Duniya
After watching a lot of this, I have come to know that the person I am sitting with today is
Bajay's manager who will be in front of you guys right now
and why Bajay is better today I will
talk to this film and if you have any problem then
what are the benefits you will get if you subscribe
you can talk to him,
you are inviting me his name is
Mr. Have you ever seen this Bajay's manager hello hello hello so
if I get it then
I still like this Rafiq I liked it very much so the
Milan Pathshala system is I believe
that in the market what does the question mean, what is the
time missed instead of land threads
a train number one capsule involved The
Amazing has a lot of votes in that budget so that is the
reason for that accident which
is the thing of gas okay one is that number one
scale
this play music good habit here
also prevents me from playing playlist Monday 09 that
you will come so you can get notifications you
can eat them but the world number 8
we  This is a little bit of rotating hormone
school to one bed full money full
front this product in nine colors
definitely we have launched more products
so please subscribe because I will
get you that the
injury looks more sweet Drishti
Kapoor had moved towards Undhiyu, I
must subscribe in this, what is the egg white product,
nothing we subscribe
customer brings, people
subscribe to it, this is definitely on Friday subscribe to
1600 on our side exam we are building
that my pregnancy is on Thursday please subscribe
and definitely subscribe
and subscribe we have loot option
[Music]
subscribe The Channel and subscribe this
Pimperkhed do intercourse at the same time list
ok ok and subscribe
because we have them white customer
[Music]
subscribe subscribe this is the way
we are, this is number one
[Music]
here if someone
already has a policy and they have been wanting to extend it for some time
now they can do it then we have a complete,
very good product, this product
is one of the account  The best product this
too this one side textbox line vin that
seems by the name that then your life okay
so you explain this to them want to
subscribe you know that those who did
not subscribe to the medical hospital channel
their everything would have been reduced in the first over two lakhs
this is the heat today their day has Italy Spain
250 dowry per sent for family Shubhendu
50% then there should be this performance Kunto a
network hospital like yours we have
dug out the loot network okay and subscribe as much as you can
subscribe and subscribe
the channel
Pacific region brother this is number one thank you ji it
feels very good talking to you let's do this now
our idiot must have understood
if someone wants to take this piece then
what do I do in MP
you can take your number in the description
don't forget to subscribe to the channel online subscribe it has become
very easy so if you
want to subscribe then
looter looter if it goes to you on Thursday
then this is nothing special for them okay okay thank you thank
you
[music]